question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Mortal Kombat was almost based on Jean-Claude Van Damme movie.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "DragonForce&#039;s &#039;Through the Fire and Flames&#039; is widely considered to be the hardest song in the Guitar Hero series.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Minecraft wasn&rsquo;t the original name to Minecraft.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "POLYBIUS is a myth arcade cabinet\/game", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Portal, the Companion Cube&#039;s ARE sentient.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "As of February 2019, the &quot;Donkey Kong Country&quot; series only had released five games (not counting remakes or ports).",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "TF2: The Heavy&#039;s voice actor, Gary Schwartz, voices the Demoman as well ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Nintendo started out as a playing card manufacturer.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "&quot;Return to Castle Wolfenstein&quot; was the only game of the Wolfenstein series where you don&#039;t play as William &quot;B.J.&quot; Blazkowicz.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Pistons were added to Minecraft in Beta 1.5.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
